1970. TOKYO. JAPAN
[person. in Japanese] Take
the first flight out to Fukuoka tomorrow.
When you get there.
someone will be waiting for you.
[Kenji] And who would that be?
[person] I want you to meet Ikeda Yuji
and hand over this briefcase.
[Kenji] Ikeda Yuji?
[person] Your business partner.
The moment you
fall out of favor with Ikeda.
the deal's over.
[door opens]
EPISODE 1: A BUSINESSMAN
[door closes]
[♪ sprightly. moody music]
[Kenji. in Korean]
My name is Matsuda Kenji.
a businessman on a work trip to Fukuoka.
My job is to deliver this briefcase safely
to Ikeda Yuji.
Press play. Subtitles appear.
200+ languages. One app:  tryray.app
[parent. in Japanese]
Hey. are you not feeling well? [chuckles]
Are you scared to fly?
-[child] I'm not scared.
-[parent] Hmm?
It's just my first time.
[parent] Everyone feels that way
their first time flying.
During takeoff.
your ears might pop a little.
It helps if you chew gum.
What do you say?
Thank you.
[parent] Good for you.
[flight attendant] Good morning. ladies
and gentlemen. This flight is scheduled…
[copilot. in English]
Japan Airways 351 cleared for takeoff.
Runway 33.
[captain] Stabilized.
[flight attendant. in Japanese]
…and arrive at Fukuoka Itazuke Airport
at around 8:50 a.m.
We will be taking off shortly.
Please be seated
and fasten your seat belt.
We will be taking off shortly.
Please be seated
and fasten your seat belt.
[captain. in English] Set takeoff thrust.
[copilot] Set takeoff thrust.
Thrust set.
Check.
[ATC] Japan Airways 351. Haneda departure.
Contact Tokyo Control 134.1.
Good day.
[flight attendant. in Japanese] Sure.
Would you like something to drink?
-[Kenji] Cola. please.
-[flight attendant. in Japanese] Sure.
[bottle hisses open]
-Here you go.
-[Kenji] Thanks.
Oh. excuse me.
Would you like something to drink?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[door opens]
Good morning.
[knocks on door]
[♪ tempestuous music]
[assailant 1] Nobody move!
[assailant 2] Don't move!
-[passengers screaming]
-Move!
[assailant 3] Don't move. or you're dead!
Don't move!
[captain. in English] Mayday. mayday.
hijacking. hijacking.
-This is Japan Air…
-[in Japanese] Stop.
We're the Revolutionary Army
of the Communist League.
Please don't kill me! Please!
Shut up and keep your heads down!
Heads down!
We're going to North Korea.
-Shut up!
-[clamoring] Hey!
[child trembling] Mom.
Are we going to die?
Shut up!
[Kenji] It's okay.
You and your mom
will make it out of here safely.
Shut up!
[Kenji. in Korean]
Japan Airways Flight 351.
a Japanese airliner that
left Tokyo Haneda Airport for Fukuoka
with 138 passengers and crew on board.
was hijacked midair.
The hijackers were the Revolutionary Army.
a radical leftist offshoot
of the Japanese Communist League.
calling themselves
the "Army for Revolutionary War."
They returned to Japan
after military training in North Korea.
and hijacked a civilian airliner.
intent on launching a revolutionary war.
Heads down! Down!
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
MINISTRY OF TRANSPORT. JAPAN
-[phone ringing]
-[chattering]
URGENT REPORT. AIRCRAFT HIJACKING
[employee 1]
We're assessing the situation.
-but it's not clear yet.
-[employee 2] Please hold on for a moment.
-Hey! No one answer the phone!
-[employee 3] Don't answer the phone!
[employee 4] Hey. hang up! Hang up!
We lost all contact
after the captain's distress signal.
I see.
MINISTER OF TRANSPORT
MORIYAMA YOSHIRO
So. what do you think we should do now?
VICE-MINISTER OF TRANSPORT
NATSUME JUNJI
We should probably report this
to the Cabinet first.
Right.
Then let's draft a report right away.
[♪ foreboding music]
[Kenji] The Revolutionary Army boarded
the plane with loads of guns and knives
with no trouble at all.
[in Japanese] Before that.
how about we notify the police first. sir?
That's a good point too.
But I'm not sure who we should call first.
Tokyo or Fukuoka police…
[Kenji. in Korean] Back then. there were
no security checks before boarding.
A manual for hijackings?
[in Japanese] Guess we'll have to check
for precedent first. huh?
[Kenji scoffs. speaks in Korean]
There was no such thing.
[in Japanese] Well.
the report should probably be addressed
to the Prime Minister. right?
That's another thing we'll need to check.
Good point.
But…
are we sure
there's been an actual hijacking?
[employee] Yes. sir. It's confirmed.
[groans]
-[hijacker 1] Keep your heads down!
-[clamoring]
Drop your hands. and you're done for!
Keep your heads down!
[alarm beeping]
[captain. in English] Turbulence.
[copilot. in Japanese]
We could go into a stall!
-Should we change course?
-What are you up to?
The weather's getting worse.
and the aircraft is unstable.
If we don't act fast. we may have
to make an emergency landing.
[hijacker 2] Then do something!
[Kenji. in Korean]
A hijacking and turbulence.
In the middle of the total chaos.
the only relief was that
Captain Honda Kunihiko was a veteran pilot
with over 10.000 flight hours.
[copilot. in Japanese]
The aircraft has stabilized.
This was supposed to be a domestic flight.
We can't make it all the way to Pyongyang.
Without more fuel.
we'll run out and crash halfway.
Yes. the captain is right.
For now. why don't we land
at Itazuke Airport as planned
and request refueling there?
They're heading to Itazuke?
[employee] Yes. sir.
[Yoshiro]
I thought they were headed to North Korea.
Why are they flying to Itazuke?
[Junji] Ah. Why indeed?
Well. we should take measures.
What kind of measures?
I mean…
[Junji inhales sharply]
-Eh?
-[Kenji] Just as the captain intended.
the plane landed safely at
its original destination. Itazuke Airport.
ITAZUKE AIRPORT. FUKUOKA. JAPAN
For a moment. it gave
the passengers some sort of hope
that this nightmare might soon be over.
[Yoshiro. in Japanese] At this point.
nothing has been confirmed.
Uh. for now. our top priority is
the safety of the passengers.
How many hijackers are on board?
Have any passengers
been killed or injured?
[reporter]
When was the last communication?
[reporter 2] Are the hijackers armed?
-Is it true they're backed by someone?
-Are all the passengers unharmed?
[reporters clamoring]
Like I said.
our top priority right now is
the safety of the passengers.
We want you
to fill the tanks.
clear the runway.
and bring us the flight charts right now.
If you don't give us what we want.
we'll start killing
the passengers one by one!
How long would it take
to fill up the tanks?
[ATC] Actually. if they're trying
to get to Pyongyang.
the fuel on board should be enough.
What are you talking about?
That's not the point.
If we want to negotiate.
we need to buy as much time as possible.
Please don't shoot.
I brought the flight charts you asked for.
Here they are.
Move!
[flight attendant yelps]
[hijacker] Damn it.
You think we're idiots?
No. There wasn't much time.
so we had to prepare them in a rush.
What about the fuel?
We're working on it now.
If you could give us a little more time…
[plane whirring in distance]
[hijacker] One passenger every hour.
If you ignore our demands.
we will kill them.
Go on.
[hijacker] Go!
[hijacker 2] Yes. sir.
Hey. just drag one out first.
[quietly] What are you doing?
Not without Mr. Yamada's orders.
The second-in-command gave the go-ahead.
We agreed to avoid unnecessary bloodshed!
If the passengers start panicking.
it'll be hard to control them.
That's the kind of thing
only weak. college-graduate types
like you worry about.
What are you standing around for?
Hey. you. Come here.
-No. wait! Please don't kill me!
-[hijacker] Come on!
[passengers screaming]
Yamagata!
Somebody help me!
[passengers screaming]
Shut up!
You want to die in his place?
Takashi. do it!
Do it!
-[♪ suspenseful music plays]
-[yells]
[hijacker] Who the hell are you?
[screaming]
You need to treat the hostages carefully
until the negotiations are over.
Since their lives are tied to yours.
[counselor panting]
[hijacker] Who the hell are you?
What do you think you're doing?
Tell your leader I want a word with him.
You think you can help us?
How exactly?
First. let the women. children.
and the elderly go.
Why should we?
[Kenji]
What you want is a revolution. isn't it?
As you know. a revolution
without public support is bound to fail.
But terrorists who release
women and children win favor
with the public and the press.
If you make the first move.
all the criticism falls on the government.
After that. whatever you do.
it's the government that takes the blame.
In the end. they'll have no choice
but to let you take off.
And you'll still have
over a hundred hostages.
Not a bad bargain. is it?
And then what?
Once you reach Pyongyang.
put the remaining passengers and crew
back on the plane
and send them home to Japan.
Then the press won't call you hijackers.
They'll paint you as heroes
who pulled off a bold operation.
Well. probably.
We can't just send the plane back.
We need to make
some kind of gesture to North Korea.
or they won't take us in.
I can provide that.
[briefcase lock clicks open]
[Yamada] That's…
[underboss] Mr. Yamada.
[Kenji] I told you.
I could help you.
Take a chance and trust me.
Do as I say. and you'll get what you want
without anyone getting hurt.
[reporter] It's opening!
[reporters clamoring]
[Kenji. in Korean] In the end. they did
what I told them and let 23 passengers go.
Women. children. and the elderly.
The meth in my briefcase was worth
nearly 90 million yen on the street.
and word was all over Japan
that the big shots in Pyongyang
were crazy for the stuff.
[Kenji scoffing] To these bastards. I was
like a jackpot that fell on their laps.
[employee. in Japanese]
They've released 23 passengers in total.
Women. children. and the elderly.
They really let them go?
[employee] Yes. sir.
But…
they're saying if we don't supply fuel
and clear the runway immediately.
they'll kill the rest of the passengers.
-[Junji] What?
-Kill them?
-What are we going to do?
-This is a problem.
This is bad.
For now. give them what they want.
The passengers' safety
is our top priority.
What do we do?
[Yoshiro sighs]
[hijacker] They're pulling back!
The fighter jets are moving!
[underboss] They're letting us take off.
We're going to Pyongyang!
[hijacker] They're fueling us up!
-We're going to Pyongyang!
-[all cheering]
Let's go to North Korea!
Why are you helping us?
It's just better to handle things quietly.
Nothing good comes
from making a lot of noise. does it?
Who are you?
As you can see.
I'm just a businessman.
[Yamada] When you say a businessman…
you mean in this kind of business. huh?
It's the best money-maker there is.
Though it comes with its risks.
[Yamada] Are you with the yakuza?
[Kenji] No.
They're more like business partners.
Something like that.
Can I bum a cigarette?
[in Korean] Is that the last one?
[in Japanese]
We're basically in the same boat now.
You can spare me a cigarette. no?
[in Korean] Oh. boy. It's his last one.
They say once you get on meth.
you can never quit.
Have you tried it?
If you're curious. why don't you
go ahead and try it now?
We're ready to take off. sir.
[♪ tense music playing]
[caller] J. A. Y. 3. 5. 1.
3. 8. 1. 1. 7.
KOREA GIMPO AIRPORT RAPCON.
(UNDERGROUND CONTROL TOWER)
[Korean airman. in English] RAPCON is
US Air Force. no Korea!
[American officer] Sergeant Chae Jiseok
is going to be here soon. all right?
He belongs to RAPCON.
Fucking let him deal with it.
We're not going
to get our hands dirty here.
[in Korean] Sir.
You called for me. sir?
[airman] As of this moment.
US Forces Korea will vacate RAPCON
and take no part in any situation
that may arise going forward.
[Jiseok]
Wait. I'm sorry. sir. I don't understand.
Who's going to be in charge here then?
[agent] Hey.
Come here.
Are you the chief controller?
Yes.
Rank and name!
Yes. sir! Sergeant Chae Jiseok.
[phone ringing]
Yes. sir.
Yes. sir. Okay.
Take it.
[director. on phone] KCIA Director here.
Are you the chief controller?
Yes. sir!
-[♪ plaintive music plays]
-[Kenji] The KCIA.
A state intelligence agency created by
the military regime that seized power
in a coup to keep its grip on the country.
Modeled after the US CIA. it operated
under the banner of anti-communism.
handling national security.
intelligence gathering.
and covert operations abroad.
But the reality was different.
Skirting the law. it terrorized the people
and wielded unchecked power.
The KCIA was nothing more
than the President's personal guard.
[director] Listen carefully
to what I'm about to say.
These are the President's orders.
In a little while.
a plane will cross over to our side.
You must seize that plane
before Pyongyang does. no matter what.
Under no circumstances should you let it
reach Pyongyang first.
Understood?
Yes. sir. Understood.
[Kenji] At last.
the plane left Itazuke Airport
and headed for Pyongyang.
But it was imperative that
we never reach Pyongyang
as the Revolutionary Army wanted.
It's better to die
than to end up in Pyongyang.
The aircraft has entered our airspace.
[captain. in English]
Any station. any station.
This is Japan Airways 351.
Japan Airways 351.
This is Seoul Control. loud and clear.
Seoul Control. this is Japan Airways 351.
Uh. we need to land at Pyongyang Airport
in North Korea.
Request any information.
Standby one.
[in Japanese]
We've got fighter jets following us.
They're Korean Air Force.
[Jiseok. in English] Japan Airways 351.
Change frequency to 131.4.
[captain] Pyongyang Control.
this is Japan Airways 351.
How do you hear me?
We want to land at Pyongyang Airport.
Request information.
Pyongyang Control. Pyongyang Control.
this is Japan Airways 351.
Radio check.
Pyongyang Control. Pyongyang Control.
This is Japan Airways 351.
Radio check.
Pyongyang Control. Pyongyang Control.
this is Japan Airways 351.
Radio check.
[Jiseok] Japan Airways 351.
this is Pyongyang Control. Loud and clear.
We control to Pyongyang Airport.
Heading 270. Maintain.
[in Japanese] Pyongyang just responded.
Congratulations. Mr. Yamada!
[Kenji] A few months prior. a flight
from Gangneung to Seoul was hijacked
and taken to North Korea
by North Korean agents
disguised as passengers.
Of the 50 people abducted.
39 returned through Panmunjom.
But 11. including the captain
and several passengers.
still remain detained in North Korea.
Chae Jiseok had been thrown
into the invisible battlefield
between the two Koreas.
[captain. in English] Pyongyang Control.
this is Japan Airways 351.
Heading 270. maintain.
Request further clearance.
[Kenji. in Korean] And now. this plane
is being hijacked all over again.
[in Japanese]
The fighter jets are pulling away. sir!
[Jiseok. in English] Japan Airways
351. this is Pyongyang Control.
Turn left heading 200.
Roger. Pyongyang Control.
Heading 200.
[Kenji. in Korean] A double hijacking.
At Gimpo Airport's control tower.
air traffic controller Chae Jiseok
intercepted the transmission
bound for Pyongyang
and redirected the plane south.
[Jiseok. in English]
Japan Airways 351. Runway 32. right.
[captain] Roger. Runway 32. right.
[Jiseok. on radio]
Good afternoon. Japan Airways 351.
Continue approach.
GIMPO AIRPORT. KOREA
[in Korean] From this moment.
this is Pyongyang Airport!
Once the hijackers exit the plane.
capture them all alive.
If they resist.
you may open fire immediately.
[Kenji] Without them realizing.
the aircraft passed over Pyongyang.
crossed the West Sea.
and finally landed at Gimpo Airport.
They cobbled together
a crowd of locals. students. and soldiers
disguised as a North Korean
welcoming committee.
They even went so far as to hang
North Korean flags on the terminal.
but the whole charade was clumsy at best.
[in Japanese] Sir. something's not right.
[Yamada] Move!
[crowd cheering]
[Kenji. in Korean] As expected.
the Revolutionary Army
sensed something was wrong.
Alas. the grand operation
they had planned…
[in English] Hey!
You!
Here. Seoul?
Yes!
[Kenji. in Korean] …ended in failure.
[in Japanese] Do you want me to kill you?
What the hell is this?
Why are we in South Korea?
I don't know.
[underboss]
You don't know? I'm going to kill you!
[Kenji] If you kill the captain.
who's going to fly the plane?
What about Pyongyang?
Not going there anymore?
I'm going to kill you.
All I did was try to help you.
Will you make it to Pyongyang
if you kill me?
Don't give me that crap.
I'm going to kill you right now.
Calm down first.
There's still a way
for you to get there safely.
[underboss] Shut up!
I'm done falling for the words
of some Zainichi.
You think I wouldn't notice?
Zainichi like you reek. you know.
That same stench you get
from pigs and dogs.
[Yamada] Stop.
There's a way for us to get to Pyongyang?
You have my word.
I'll get you to Pyongyang safely.
Are you willing to bet your life on that?
I'll bet my life on it.
[Kenji. in Korean] Japan.
closely monitoring the plane's movements.
was thrown into complete chaos
and dispatched a delegation
to South Korea to assess the situation.
[official] I don't know how
the plane ended up landing here.
But now that it's in our country. there is
no way we're sending it to Pyongyang.
[interpreter. in Japanese] "There's no way
we're sending it to Pyongyang."
[mic feedback]
[Junji]
The mic. Mr. Jeong. the microphone switch.
-What about it?
-The microphone.
[interpreter 2] Right. sorry.
[in Japanese] Who'd want to send it
to Pyongyang? None of us wants that.
"Who'd want to send it to Pyongyang?"
But listen.
With the passengers' lives at stake.
we need to leave room for negotiation.
[clicks mic button]
[in Korean] So why did you let it
come here in the first place?
This should've been handled in Japan!
[interpreter]
"It should've been handled in Japan."
This really puts us
in a difficult position too.
but the President's stance
is absolutely firm.
[interpreter. in Japanese]
"…is absolutely firm."
[Yoshiro]
We're well aware that public opinion
in South Korea isn't favorable
because of the recent hijacking incident.
But there are more than a hundred lives
on the line here.
So shouldn't we approach this
from a humanitarian perspective
rather than a political one?
[in Korean] Look. it's not public opinion
we're concerned about.
Our priority is the safety
of the South Korean aircraft
and citizens still held in the North.
We're not saying
you can't negotiate with them.
We're saying sending it to Pyongyang is
-absolutely out of the question.
-[official] That's right…
-[mic feedback]
-[feedback stops]
-[minister] Geez. what…
-[official] That's right.
After all. if we don't start
the engines from outside.
-the plane can't even take off.
-[interpreter translates]
They're not some miracle workers.
are they?
In the end.
they'll have no choice but to give in.
The South Korean government never admitted
that it had deliberately
diverted the plane.
[Junji. in Japanese] On that plane
are our citizens.
Japanese citizens.
They're completely innocent people.
just like you.
We fully understand the position
of the South Korean government.
But right now. please put
the passengers' lives
and safety above all else.
I sincerely urge you.
[Kenji. in Korean]
The gap between the two sides was clear.
and there was little sign of compromise.
[captain. in English]
This is Japan Airways 351.
-We need air in the cabin.
-[passengers coughing]
The engines have shut down.
and all the power
and ventilation systems are down.
Unless we get air
into the cabin immediately.
it will be difficult to breathe.
I repeat.
We need air in the cabin.
-The engines have shut down…
-[slurping]
…and all the power
and ventilations are down.
Unless we get air
into the cabin immediately.
it will be difficult to breathe.
This is Seoul Approach Control.
Open the door.
Once again. open the door.
[Yamada. in Japanese] Like you said.
we pinned all the blame
on the Japanese government.
Good.
[clears throat] The Japanese government is
probably trying to figure out a way
to send you to Pyongyang
for the passengers' safety.
The problem is
the South Korean government.
They won't let you go that easily.
I owe you one.
So what's your plan?
You need a justification.
Let all the remaining passengers go.
You bastard. You think
we're going to fall for that again?
Hey.
Who the hell are you. really?
I told you.
I'm a businessman.
What are you playing at?
[clicks tongue. sighs]
All I want is to settle this quietly.
Send you to Pyongyang
and finish my business.
We're not letting any more passengers go.
If the South Korean government
doesn't accept our demands.
we're killing them all!
And of course.
we'll cut your head off first.
Fine.
Then let's do it another way.
Bring me the briefcase I gave you.
Inside is the answer
to get you to Pyongyang.
[briefcase lock clicks open]
[♪ thrilling music playing]
[Yamada groans]
[hijackers grunt]
[underboss yells. grunts]
[hijacker yells]
[grunts]
[underboss yelling]
[underboss grunts]
[hijacker breathing shakily]
[passengers scream]
[hijacker breathes shakily] What was that?
Was that a gunshot?
[hijacker 2] What? We've got guns?
[grunting]
[underboss] Put the gun down now.
Otherwise.
we all die together.
-Go ahead.
-[♪ precarious music plays]
Come on. do it.
[in Korean] They heard a gunshot
from inside the plane.
[interpreter] They heard a gunshot
from inside the plane!
[minister] A gunshot?
-Good grief.
-Really?
[in Japanese] As you just saw.
this isn't like the toys you're holding.
This one can actually kill.
So.
what are you going to do to us?
[Kenji] From now on.
you're going to quietly follow
my orders and go to Pyongyang.
[Kenji. in Korean] That's right.
They took the passengers
hostage to seize the plane.
Now. I'll take them hostage
to get out of here.
[in Japanese] From here on.
tell them exactly what I'm about to say.
We want…
[Yamada] We want nothing more than that.
[airman. in Korean]
"We want nothing more than that."
[Yamada. in Japanese]
If you don't meet our demands…
"If you don't meet our demands…"
[Yamada. in Japanese]
…the second it hits noon…
"…the second it hits noon…"
[Yamada] …we'll detonate the bomb
on this plane and blow ourselves up.
"…we'll detonate the bomb
on this plane and blow ourselves up."
[Yamada. in Japanese]
But if you do what we ask…
"But if you do what we ask…"
[Yamada. in Japanese]
…we will safely release…
[interpreter. in Korean]
"…we will safely release…"
[Yamada. in Japanese] …all the passengers.
[interpreter. in Korean]
"…all the passengers."
[agent scoffs]
[in Japanese] Thank goodness.
How can we trust them to keep their word?
To show good faith. they said
they'd release half the passengers now.
Fifty-eight in total.
[Yoshiro]
They're actually releasing the passengers?
[Kenji. in Korean] Hostage exchange.
-The condition I had Yamada deliver
-[♪ intriguing music]
was that a senior Japanese government
official would take the place
of the passengers
and become the hijackers' hostage.
I was a Japanese businessman
who boarded the plane with drugs.
To get out of the mess
without ending up in North Korea.
I had to find a way to settle it.
With a new hostage. the Revolutionary Army
secured their own safety.
while South Korea's justification
for grounding the plane.
citing passenger safety.
was no longer valid.
North Korea granted
the Revolutionary Army asylum.
and just as I expected.
the plane was sent back to Japan
a few days later.
They couldn't ignore the glare
of the international community.
Once repatriated. Vice-Minister Natsume
and Captain Honda were celebrated
as national heroes in Japan parlaying
that fame into politics and success.
But Chae Jiseok. the controller
who diverted the plane
and saved the passengers.
was never hailed as a hero.
Instead. he was pressured into silence
about what happened that day.
until he finally hung up
his uniform for good.
That's right.
That's how the President and the KCIA
keep this country running.
-[reporter 1] Here he comes!
-[reporter 2] Hey. he's here!
[shutters clicking]
GIMPO INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
[official] We share the joy
of the safe rescue
of the abducted passengers in Seoul
with the free people of the world.
On this occasion.
our government and our people have
once again renewed our vigilance
against the atrocities
of the communist forces.
[Kenji] After the incident.
Japan started airport security checks
and even enacted an anti-hijacking law
which meant the good old days
of casually boarding a plane
with a briefcase full of drugs were over.
Too bad about that briefcase.
but leaving it was the right call.
[in Japanese] It's a gift.
I doubt we'll ever see
each other again. but…
For your silence.
ITAZUKE AIRPORT. FUKUOKA. JAPAN
[Kenji. in Korean] And so.
I arrived in Fukuoka later than planned.
There'd been a bit of trouble.
but business is business.
Finally. I was about
to meet my business partner. Ikeda Yuji.
Is it a woman?
It's a woman.
I was told I had to go through her
to reach Chairman Ikeda.
and the moment I fell out of her favor.
the deal was over.
[in Japanese] I'm Ikeda Yuji.
I'm Matsuda Kenji.
You're very late.
Something came up.
The goods?
Can I borrow a light?
I left the goods on the plane.
I had to because of
the Revolutionary Army.
Are you talking about the plane
that went to Pyongyang?
That's the one. I was on it.
I'm sorry.
But I suppose
this is where our business ends.
Farewell.
It's a shame.
I was hoping to show Chairman Ikeda
the best there is.
I'll see you again.
[engine starts]
[in Korean] Damn it.
This hill's killing me.
BUSAN DISTRICT
PROSECUTORS' OFFICE. KOREA
[Geonyoung] It's killing me. [panting]
[newscaster]
After nerve-racking negotiations.
Japan's Vice-Minister of Transport.
Natsume. boarded the plane
-as a hostage himself…
-Wow.
I thought they were
just a bunch of clueless idiots.
But it looks like at least one of them
-knew how to use his head.
-[investigator] Yeah. pretty clever.
Back to work. people.
-Yes. Mr. Jang.
-Yes. sir.
-Come on.
[Geonyoung] Oh. boy.
-[Geonyoung] Mr. Kim.
-[Investigator Kim] Yes?
[Geonyoung] The Manjae Gang's movements
lately. Doesn't it bother you?
[Investigator Kim] Yeah.
[Geonyoung] I mean. are these punks
trying to turn themselves
-into export heroes by dealing meth?
-Right.
Why do they keep getting involved
with the yakuza?
-[Investigator Kim] I know. right?
-Who is this?
Uh… We still haven't been able
to identify him. sir.
[Geonyoung breathes deeply]
MEETING BETWEEN JO MANJAE
AND AN UNIDENTIFIED MALE IN A SUIT…
[♪ ominous music playing]
[sighs]
[officer] Baek!
Come here.
Did you enjoy your vacation?
It must've been nice.
You call a business trip a vacation?
Where are you going? The boss is in there.
[overlapping chattering]
-Start talking! I said start talking! Hey!
-[metallic crash]
[person screams]
[loud crashing. thudding]
Move it. asshole! Hey!
[water splashes]
[officer 4]
Talk. you bastard. Talk! I said. talk!
[grunting]
Hey. come here. you bastard!
Spit it out! Spit it out now!
[Kenji] You wanted to see me. sir?
-[officer] Hey. you're here.
-[screaming]
Good work out there.
Let's go talk in my office.
Hey! Start talking. you bastard!
Get the hell up now!
[♪ classical music playing]
[director sighs]
DIRECTOR GENERAL HWANG GUKPYEONG
What've you got there?
Uh. I got you some whiskey and cigars.
Come on.
You didn't have to.
[sighs]
Damn it. It got on me.
Hey. I liked it.
The double hijacking. Good idea.
Thank you. sir.
[Gukpyeong]
The higher-ups can't stop raving about it.
351 DOUBLE HIJACKING GIMPO
BAEK KITAE
[Kenji. in English] DHJ. double hijacking.
JAY351 REQUESTING
DOUBLE HIJACKING AT GIMPO AIRPORT
My code number. B73.
I had given the boy's mother
the KCIA emergency number.
"3. 8. 1. 1. 7. 7…"
[Kenji. in Korean] And thankfully.
she stayed calm and made the call.
[in Japanese] 6. 7. 1. B. 7. 3…
[Kenji. in Korean] The KCIA
moved quickly. and just as I had planned…
the plane bound for Pyongyang
landed at Gimpo Airport.
-[Gukpyeong] Anyway…
-[lighter clicks]
…about Jo Manjae.
I hear he's been dealing meth
with the yakuza.
Yes. I'm aware.
You're aware?
Yes. sir.
So why didn't you report it to me?
Mr. Baek?
Baek Kitae.
[Kitae] That's right.
My name is Baek Kitae.
Head of the Intelligence Department.
KCIA Busan Branch.
[♪ sprightly. moody music plays]
Translated by Yoonjung Song
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today